Aidan Nagorcka-Smith

0412 535 563 aidanns@gmail.com

Summary

About me:

After finishing high school in 2007, I moved from rural Victoria to inner Melbourne so that I could take up a place in the Bachelor of Science at The University of Melbourne, where I was offered a scholarship. Since then I have lived, studied and worked in the city, finding success in all three endeavours. I am currently studying for the Master of Engineering at the University of Melbourne, where I am also employed as a tutor and research assistant.

I always attempt to lead a balanced lifestyle, making sure to always take pleasure in both work and study. In my spare time I enjoy playing guitar, jogging, snowboarding, rock climbing, video games and a healthy social life with my friends.

While I enjoy and am committed to personal success, my long term goal is to be involved in projects that will bring positive outcomes to the wider community, both here in Australia and abroad.

General Qualities:

- Outgoing and friendly, while patient when needed.
- A quick learner and able to think intuitively in order to solve problems, yet not afraid to ask for help when it's needed.
- Highly ethical and trustworthy.
- Able to work effectively without supervision or in a group situation.
- Physically, mentally and emotionally healthy.

Employment History

The University of Melbourne - Research Assistant

(December 2011 - current)

Full lifecycle software development for the Melbourne University Game-based Learning Environment, a joint research/teach tool from the department of Computing and Information Systems.

The University of Melbourne - Tutor

(March 2011 - current)

- Lead group based tutorials and aid in individual learning through workshops at the undergraduate level.
- Provide input in to subject design, including both theory and practical components.
- Mark student projects and exams.

Univex Software - Software Trainer and Support Technician (March 2008 - December 2010)

- Deliver and support variety of IT systems and services for both internal staff and customers.
- Streamline business activities through internal documentation and systemisation in areas such as internal documentation, automated monitoring and staff training.

Currently studying:

Master of Engineering (Software Engineering), The University of Melbourne (2013 expected completion)

Qualifications:

Bachelor of Science (Computer Science), The University of Melbourne (December 2010)

Victorian Certificate of Education (VCE), Bayview College, Portland (Dec 2006)

Cisco Certified Network Associate Units 1 - 4 (CCNA), South West Tafe, Portland (June 2005 – Oct 2006)

Significant achievements and awards:

- Excellence in Tutoring award, Department of Computer Science and Software Engineering, The University of Melbourne, Semester 1, 2011.
- Consistently high grades across a variety off university subjects, with a total GPA of 82.04 (86.67 major) for my Bachelor of Science and 80.86 for my Master of Engineering, both representing first class honours.
- Achieving an ENTER of 98.8, placing me academically in the top 1.2% of students completing year 12 in 2007.
- Perfect Score and Premiers Award for Excellence in Information Technology, a year 12 subject I completed in year 11, placing me in the top five Information Technology students of 2006.
- Completing my VCE at the end of year 11, one full year ahead of time.
- Westvic Workforce VCE VET award for Excellence 2006 for outstanding results in Cisco CCNA over the year of 2006.